Finding Aid for the Republic Pictures Corporation Records LSC.0979
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Continuity Scripts
  - The Quiet Man. (Box 22)
    Cast: John Wayne, Maureen O'Hara Barry Fitzgerald, Ward Bond
  - South of Rio., 1949.; 10 copies.
    Cast: Monte Hale, Kay Christopher
  - South of Rio., 1949.; 7 copies.
  - The Mysterious Mr. Valentin., 1946.; 25 copies. (Box 6)
    Cast: William Henry, Linda Stirling
  - The Mysterious Mr. Valentine., 1946.; 5 copies. (Box 6)
    Cast: William Henry, Linda Stirling, Virginia Christine
  - The Mysterious Mr. Valentine., 1946.; 1 copy. (Box 6)
  - Tillers of The Soil (short subject)., 1950.; 10 copies. (Box *)
  - The Big Show Off., 1944.; 4 copies. (Box 23)
    Cast: Arthur Lake, Dale Evans
  - Stagecoach to Monterey., 1944.; 10 copies. (Box ??)
    Cast: Allen Lane, Peggy Stewart, Twinkle Watts
  - Tumbling Tumbleweeds., 1935.; 10 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette, Lucille Brown
  - Train To Alcatraz., 1948.; 5 copies. (Box 46)
    Cast: Donald Barry, Janet Martin, William Phipps
    - Trailer., 20 copies.
  - Unmasked., 1950.; 4 copies. (Box 46)
    Cast: Robert Rockwell, Barbra Fuller, Raymond Burr, Hillary Brooke
  - Honeychile., 1951.; 4 copies. (Box 46)
    Cast: Judy Canova, Eddie Foy Jr., Alan Hale, Jr.
  - Homicide For Three., 1948.; 3 copies. (Box 46)
    Cast: Audrey Long, Warren Douglas, Grant Withers
  - The Invisible Informer., 1946.; 3 copies. (Box 46)
    Cast: Linda Stirling, William Henry, Adele Mara, Gerald Mohr
  - I Was a Convict., 1939.; 2 copies. (Box 46)
    Cast: Barton MacLane, Beverly Roberts, Clarence Kolb
  - I'll Reach For a Star., 1937.; 2 copies. (Box 46)
    Cast: Frances Langford, Phil Regan, Louise Hentry, Pert Kelton
  - In Old California., 1942.; 2 copies. (Box 12)
    Cast: John Wayne, Binnie Barnes, Albert Dekker
  - The El Paso Kid., 1946.; 23 copies. (Box 44)
    Cast: Sunset Carson, Marie Harmon, Hank Patterson
  - The Great Train Robbery., 1941.; 5 copies. (Box 2)
    Cast: Bob Steele, Claire Carleton, Milburn Stone, Monte Blue
  - Oh! Susanna., 1951..; 2 copies. (Box 46)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Adrian Booth, Forest Tucker, Chill Wills
  - Grissly's Millions., 1944.; 3 copies. (Box 29)
    Cast: Paul Kelly, Virginia Grey, Don Douglas
    - Grissly's Millions. (trailer)., 1944; 10 copies.
  - Spotted List (English)., 20 copies.
  - Trailer., 20 copies.
  - Melody and Moonlight., 1940.; 3 copies. (Box 38)
    Cast: Johnny Downs, Barbara Allen, Jerry Colonna
  - (Trailer)., 28 copies.
  - Red River Range., 1938.; 3 copies. (Box -)
  - Above Us the Waves., 1955.; 1 copy. (Box -)
    Cast: John Mills, Donald Sinden, John Gregson, Theodore Bikel
  - I've Always Loved You., 1 copy. (Box -)
    Cast: Philip Dorn, Catherine McLeod, Mma. Maria Ouspenskaya
  - Leavenworth Case., 1936.; 1 copy. (Box -)
    Cast: Donald Cook, Jean Ruverol, Norman Foster, Erin O'Brien-Moore
  - Jealousy., 1945.; 9 copies. (Box -)
    Director: Gustav Machaty
    Cast: John Loder, Jane Randolph, Karen Morley, Nils Asther
  - Captain Tugboat Annie., 1945.; 10 copies. (Box -)
    Cast: Jane Darwell, Edgar Kennedy, Charles Gordon, H.B. Warner
  - A Lawman Is Born., 3 copies. (Box -)
    Cast: Johnny Mack Brown, Iris Meredith, Warner Richmond, Mary MacLaren
- Shooting Scripts
  - Accused of Murder [2026].; sw: Bob Williams., 1956 (Box 70, 130)
  - The Admiral Hoskins Story [1976].; sw: Allen Rivkin; series: Deluxe., 1954 (Box 62, 82, 83, 118)
  - Affairs of Cappy Ricks [645]., 1937. (Box 105)
  - Affairs of Jimmy Valentine [1093]., 1942. (Box 85, 96)
  - Alaska Frontier [1st draft] [1908].; sw: Albert DeMond; series: Variety., 1950 (Box 66)
  - Alcatraz Prison Train [1748].; sw: Gerald Geraghty; series: Variety., 1948 (Box 102)
  - Alias Billy the Kid [1536].; sw: Earle Snell and Betty Burbridge; series:, 1945 1945. (Box 121)
  - All the Tomorrows [867]., 1939. (Box 64)
  - Along the Navajo Trail [1425].; sw: Gerald Geraghty; series: Rogers-premiere., 1945 (Box 68)
  - Along the Oregon Trail [1676].; sw: Earle Snell; series: All Star., 1947 (Box 122)
  - An Old Spanish Custom [1922].; sw: Jack Townley, Charles E. Roberts; series: Estelita Special., 1951 (Box 84, 108)
  - And Suddenly You Run [1985].; sw: John K. Butler., 1955 (Box 102)
  - Angels in Exile [1673].; sw: Charles Larson; series: Deluxe., 1948 (Box 62)
  - Angels With Broken Wings [1057]., 1941. (Box 132)
  - Apache Rose [1526].; sw: Gerald Geraghty; series: Roy Rogers Premiere., 1946 (Box 123)
  - The Arizona Cowboy [1800].; sw: Bradford Ropes; series: All Star., 1949 (Box 83)
  - Arizona Kid [921]., 1939. (Box 71)
  - Arkansas Judge [993]., 1940. (Box 75)
  - Army Girl [631]., 1937. (Box 90)
  - Atlantic City [1245]., 1944. (Box 112)
  - The Atomic Kid [1972].; sw: Benedict Freedman & John F. Murray & Blake Edwards; series: Deluxe., 1954 (Box 131)
  - Back in the Saddle [1003]., 1941. (Box 71)
  - Bad Man of Deadwood [1024]., 1941. (Box 135)
  - Bal Tabarin [1925].; sw: Houstan Branch; series: New Master., 1951 (Box 108)
  - Bandit King of Texas [1725].; sw: Olive Cooper; series: Famous Western., 1949 (Box 117)
  - Bandits of Dark Canyon [1712].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Famous Western., 1947 (Box 89)
  - Bandit of the Badlands [1531].; sw: Doris Schroeder; series: Superior Western., 1945 (Box 121)
  - Barnyard Follies [1045]., 1940. (Box 132)
  - Behind the News [1049]., 1940. (Box 132)
  - Belle Le Grand [1755].; sw: D.D. Beauchamp., 1948 (Box 83, 109)
  - Belle of Old Mexico [1773].; sw: Bradford Ropes, Francis Swan; series: Special., 1949 (Box 101)
  - Bells of Capistrano [1203]., 1942. (Box 92)
  - Bells of Rosarita [1324].; sw: Jack Townley, series: Premiere., 1944 (Box 81)
  - Bells of San Angelo [1525].; sw: Sloan Nibley; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1946 (Box 122)
  - Beneath Western Skies [1404]., 1943. (Box 119)
  - Beware of Ladies [646]., 1936. (Box 104)
  - Beyond the Last Frontier [1401]., 1943. (Box 81)
  - Behind the Ships [1454];; sw: Dane Lussier; series: Jubilee., 1944 (Box 100)
  - The Big Bonanza [1274].; sw: Robert Presnell; Leonard Praskins., 1944 (Box 118)
  - The Big Jackpot [1981].; sw: Houston Branch; series: Jubilee., 1955 (Box 83)
  - The Big Show [607]., 1936. (Box 104)
  - Bill Cracks Down [680]., 1937. (Box 79)
  - Billy the Kid Returns [R 1].; series:., 1938 ?. (Box 131)
  - The Black Hills [1770].; sw: Charles Marquis Warren; series: Deluxe., 1950 (Box 102)
  - Black Hills Ambush [1739].; sw: Ronald Davidson, M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1951 (Box 117)
  - The Blocked Trail [1213].; series: Mesquiteers., 1942 (Box 116)
  - The Blonde Bandit [1777].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1949 (Box 102)
  - The Bold Frontiersman [1714].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Famous Western., 1947 (Box 88)
  - Border Legion [1021]., 1940. (Box 135)
  - Border Saddlemates [1813].; sw: Albert DeMond; series: Paramount., 1951 (Box 109)
  - Bordertown Gunfighters [1306]., 1943. (Box 119)
  - Born to Be Wild [756]., 1938. (Box 80)
  - Bowery Boy [951]., 1940. (Box 74)
  - Brazil [1193].; sw: Frank Gill, Jr., Laura Kerr., 1944 (Box 92)
  - Brimstone [1761].; sw: Thames Williamson; series: Deluxe., 1948 (Box 101)
  - Brother Van [1903].; sw: Warren Duff; series: Deluxe., 1955 (Box 83)
  - Bulldog Edition [673]., 1936. (Box 78)
  - Calendar Girl [1486].; sw: Mary Loos, Richard Sale; series: Deluxe., 1946 (Box 64)
  - California Firebrand [1679].; sw: John K. Butler, J. Benton Cheney; series: All Star., 1947 (Box 84)
  - California Gold Rush [1513].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Red Ryder Western., 1945 (Box 66)
  - Call of the Canyon [1202]., 1942. (Box 91)
  - Call of the Rockies [1407]., 1944. (Box 119)
  - Call of the South Seas [1249]., 1944. (Box 117)
  - Calling All Marines [835]., 1939. (Box 127)
  - Calling Wild Bill Elliott [1301]., 1943. (Box 81)
  - Campus Honeymoon [1657].; sw: Richard Sale; series: Variety., 1947 (Box 135)
  - Candlelights in Lisbon [1255]., 1944. (Box 111)
  - Captain Jan [1954].; sw: John K. Butler; series; Deluxe., 1952 (Box 97)
  - Captive of Billy the Kid [1738].; sw: Richard Wormser, M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1951 (Box 90)
  - Carolina Cannonball [6035].; sw: Barry Shipman; series: Peerless., 1954 (Box 129)
  - Carolina Moon [908].; sw:?; series: Autry., 1940 (Box 105)
  - Carson City Raiders [1716].; sw: Earle Snell; series: Famous Western., 1948 (Box 64)
  - The Catman of Paris [1556].; sw: Sherman L. Lowe; series: Anniversary., 1945 (Box 103)
  - A Certain Lady [1086], 1941. (Box 89)
  - Chatterbox [1156]., 1942. (Box 97)
  - The Cherokee Flash [1532].; sw: Betty Burbridge; series: Superior Western., 1945 (Box 122)
  - Cheyenne Wildcat [1413]., 1944. (Box 111)
  - The Chicago Kid [1166].; sw: Jack Townley; series: Anniversary., 1944 (Box 92)
  - Citizen Soldier [1924].; sw: Mary McCall, Jr.; series: Deluxe., 1951 (Box 83, 84, 134)
  - City That Never Sleeps [1768?].; sw: Steve Fisher; series: Deluxe., 1952 (Box 66)
  - Code of the Outlaw [1116].; sw:?; series: Mesquiteers., 1941 (Box 65)
  - Code of the Prairie [1431].; sw: Albert DoMond, Anthony Coldeway., 1944 (Box 77)
  - Code of the Silver Sage [1728].; sw: Arthur E. Orloff; series: Famous Western., 1949 (Box 90)
  - Colorado Pioneers [1512]. sw: Earle Snell; series: Red Ryder Western., 1945: (Box 88)
  - Colorado Sundown [1842].; sw: Eric Taylor; William Lively; series: Paramount., 1951 (Box 114)
  - Colorado Sunset [805].; series: Autry., 1939 (Box 127)
  - Come On, Cowboys [625].; sw:?; series: Mesquiteers., 1937 (Box 76)
  - Come On, Leathernecks [733]., 1938. (Box 82)
  - Come Next Spring [2000].; sw: Montgomery Pittman, Lillie Hayward; series: Deluxe., 1955 (Box 99)
  - Concerto [1551].; sw: Borden Chase; Series: Deluxe, 1945 (Box 137)
  - The Congress Dances [5539]., 1956. (Box 129)
  - Conquest of Cheyenne [1515].; sw: Earle Snell; series: Red Ryder Western., 1945 (Box 123)
  - Corpus Christi Bandits [A405].; sw: Norman S. Hall; series: Action Western., 1944 (Box 131)
  - Country Fair [1058]., 1941. (Box 132)
  - Country Gentlemen [3523]., 1936. (Box 114)
  - Covered Trailer [969]., 1939. (Box 75)
  - Covered Wagon Raid [1730].; sw: Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1950 (Box 90)
  - Cowboy and the Señorita [1321]., 1943. (Box 73)
  - Cowboy Serenade [1104].; sw:?; series: Autry., 1941 (Box 67)
  - Crime of the Century [1493].; sw: O'Leta Rinehart, William Hagens, Getrude Walker; series: Jubilee., 1945 (Box 88)
  - Crooked Road [990]., 1940. (Box 112)
  - Crosswinds [1759].; sw: Gerald Geraghty, Thames Williamson; series: Deluxe., 1949 (Box 66)
  - Cuban Fireball [1786].; sw: Charles E. Roberts, Jack Townley; series: Comedy Special., 1950 (Box 85)
  - Dakota [1543].; sw: Lawrence Hazard; series: Deluxe., 1945 (Box 137)
  - Dakota Incident [2024].; sw: Frederick Louis Fox; series: Deluxe., 1955 (Box 130, 131)
  - The Dakota Kid [6027].; sw: William Lively: series: Adventure Western., 1950 (Box 114)
  - Dancing Feet [3525]., 1936. (Box 114)
  - The Danger Trail [1940]. [Formerly The Golden Herd]. sw: Steve Fisher., 1952. (Box 87)
  - Dangerous Holiday [674]., 1937. (Box 76)
  - Daredevils of the Clouds [1649].; sw: Norman S. Hall; series: Variety., 1948 (Box 137)
  - A Daring Holiday [1472].; sw: Bradford Ropes., 1944 (Box 101)
  - Dark Command [972]., 1939. (Box 79)
  - Daughter of the Jungle [1749].; sw: William Lively; series: Variety., 1948 (Box 113)
  - Daybreak [1035]. sw: Niven Busch., 1949: (Box 133)
  - Days of Jesse James [923]., 1939. (Box 75)
  - Death in the Sands [1796].; sw: James Edward Grant., 1950 (Box 65)
  - Death Valley Gunfighter [1721].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Famous western., 1949 (Box 77)
  - Death Valley Manhunt [1307]., 1943. (Box 118)
  - Deerslayer [un-numbered].; sw: John W. Krafft., 1943 (Box 81)
  - The Denver Kid [1718].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Famous Western., 1948 (Box 72)
  - Desert of Lost Men [1735].; sw: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1951 (Box 88)
  - Desert Trail Riders [715].; sw:?; series: Mesquiteers., 1938 (Box 86)
  - Desperadoes of Dakota [1511].; sw: Earle Snell; series: Red Ryder Western., 1945 (Box 72)
  - Desperadoes of Dodge City [1715].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Famous Western., 1948 (Box 64)
  - Desperadoes' Outpost [1877].; sw: Arthur Orloff, Albert DeMond; series: Famous Western., 1952 (Box 93)
  - Desperate Adventure [741]., 1938. (Box 80)
  - Destination Big House [1784].; sw: Eric Taylor; series: Variety., 1950 (Box 103)
  - The Devil Pays Off [988].; sw: M.S. Boylan., 1941 (Box 71, 138)
  - Dr. Judith Randall [799].; sw: Joseph M. March; series: Jubilee., 1938 (Box 127)
  - Don't Fence Me In [1327].; sw: Darrell and Stuart McGowan; series: Rogers-premiere., 1945 (Box 120)
  - Down Dakota Way [1628].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Rogers premiere., 1949 (Box 107)
  - Down Mexico Way [1009]., 1941. (Box 71)
  - Driftwood [1581].; sw: Mary Loos and Richard Sale; series: Deluxe., 1947 (Box 121)
  - Duel at Apache Wells [2030].; sw: Bob Williams., 1956 (Box 107, 131)
  - The Duke Comes Back [759]., 1939. (Box 126)
  - Duke of Chicago [1742].; sw: Albert DeMond; series: Variety., 1948 (Box 79)
  - Earl Carroll's Sketch Book [1570].; sw: Frank Gill, Jr. & Parke Levy; series: Deluxe., 1946 (Box 123)
  - Earl Carroll's Vanities [1451].; sw: Frank Gill, Jr., 1944 (Box 101)
  - The El Paso Kid [1535].; sw: Norman Sheldon; series: Superior Western., 1946 (Box 121)
  - El Paso Stampede [1881].; sw: Dwight Babcock; series: series: Famous Western., 1952 (Box 99)
  - El Paso Stampede [6029].; sw: Arthur Orloff; series: Famous Western., 1953
  - End of the Rainbow [1656].; sw: Mary Loos, Richard Sale; series: Deluxe., 1947 (Box 136)
  - End of the Road [1442].; sw: Denison Clift, Gertrude Walker., 1944 (Box 100)
  - Escape by Night [773]., 1937. (Box 127)
  - Ever Since Adam [645]., n.d. (Box 72)
  - Everything Happens to Us [744].; sw: Paul Gerard Smith and Richard English; series: Showmen's., 1938
  - Exiled to Shanghai [765]., 1938. (Box 126)
  - Exposed [1672].; sw: Royal Cole, Charles Moran; series: Variety., 1947 (Box 100)
  - Eyes of Texas [1623].; sw: Nibley, Sloan; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1948 (Box 89)
  - The Fabulous Nellie Bly [1915].; sw: Irwin Gielgud; series: Deluxe., 1951 (Box 66)
  - The Fabulous Texan [1450].; sw: Lawrence Hazard, Horace McCoy; series: Deluxe., 1947 (Box 101, 106)
  - Faces in the Sun [1760]., 1949. (Box 66)
  - Faces in the Fog [1446].; sw: Jack Townley; series: ?????, 1944 (Box 106)
  - False Faces [1181]., 1943. (Box 115)
  - The Far Frontier [1626].; sw: Sloan Nibley; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1948 (Box 100)
  - The Fatal Witness [1485].; sw: Jerry Sackheim; series: Jubilee., 1944 (Box 72)
  - Federal Agent at Large [1774].; sw: Albert DeMond; series: Variety., 1949 (Box 102)
  - Fighting Searchers [1189]., 1943. (Box 116)
  - Fighting Thoroughbreds [868]., 1938. (Box 63)
  - Fighting U.S. Coast Guard [1910].; sw: Kenneth Gamet; series: Deluxe., 1950 (Box 108)
  - Fire Over the Waterfront [679].; sw: Peggy Thompson., 1938 (Box 78)
  - Firebrands of Arizona [1432].; sw: Randall Fayo., 1944 (Box 105)
  - The First Color Picture [423?]., n.d. (Box 76)
  - First Prize [768].; sw: Gordon Kahn., 1938 (Box 126)
  - The Flame [1571].; sw: Lawrence Kimble; series: Deluxe., 1947 (Box 121)
  - Flame of the Barbary Coast [1269].; sw: Borden Chase., 1944 (Box 68, 82)
  - Flaming Fury [1764].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1949 (Box 85)
  - Flight at Midnight [862].; sw: John Monk Saunders., 1939 (Box 63)
  - Flight from Fury [1916].; sw: Milton M. Raison; series: Variety., 1951 (Box 83)
  - Flight Nurse [1927].; sw: Alan LeMay; series: Deluxe., 1953 (Box 85)
  - Follow Your Heart [3509]., 1936. (Box 98)
  - Follow Your Star [1950].; sw: Houston Branch; series: Deluxe., 1952 (Box 94, 95)
  - For Your Eyes Only [1975].; sw: Philip Yordan; series: Deluxe., 1954 (Box 62)
  - Forged Passport [865]., 1938. (Box 63)
  - Forgotten Girls [961]., 1940. (Box 86)
  - Fort Dodge Stampede [1737].; sw: Richard Wormser; series: Famous Western., 1951 (Box 73)
  - Friendly Neighbors [1033]., 1940. (Box 133)
  - Frisco Tornado [1732].; sw: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1950 (Box 89)
  - Frontier Doctor [5374].; [The Double Cross--working title]; sw: Ronald Davidson; series: T.V., 1956 (Box 138)
  - Frontier Doctor [5375].; [Cattle War--working title]; sw: Maurico Tombragel; series: T.V., 1956 (Box 125)
  - Frontier Doctor [5376].; [Canadian Adventure--working title]; sw: Joe Richardson; series: T.V., 1956 (Box 125)
  - Frontier Doctor [5377].; [White Man's Plague--working title]; sw: Milton M. Raison; series: T.V., 1956 (Box 125)
  - Frontier Doctor [5378].; [Uncharted Trails--working title]; sw: Maurice Tombragel; series: T.V., 1956 (Box 125, 139)
  - Frontier Doctor [5379].; [Old Rebel--working title]; sw: Barry Shipman; series: T.V., 1956 (Box 139)
  - Frontier Doctor [5380].; [Gypsy Trails--working title]; sw: Sloan Nibley; series: T.V., 1956 (Box 139)
  - Frontier Investigator [1722].; sw: Bob Williams; series: Famous Western., 1949 (Box 90)
  - The Gallant Legion [1148].; sw: Gerald Adams; series: Deluxe., 1947 (Box 97)
  - The Gangs of Chicago [963]., 1940. (Box 72)
  - Gangs of Sonora [1019]., 1941. (Box 136)
  - Gangs of the Waterfront [1462].; sw: Albert Beich; series: Jubillee., 1944 (Box 100)
  - Gaucho Serenade [903].; series: Autry., 1940 (Box 73)
  - Gauchos of El Dorado [1113].; series: Mesquiteer., n.d. (Box 126)
  - Gay Blades [1467];; sw: Albert Beich; series: Victory., 1945 (Box 110)
  - The Gay Ranchero [1528].; sw: Sloan Nibley; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1947 (Box 122)
  - Gay Vagabond [1062]., 1941. (Box 118)
  - The Gentleman from London [746]., 1938. (Box 75)
  - Geraldine [1955].; sw: Peter Milne, Frank Gill, Jr.; series: Deluxe., 1953 (Box 97)
  - The Ghost Goes Wild [1466].; sw: Randall Faye; series: Victory., 1946 (Box 101)
  - Girl from Alaska [1094]., 1942. (Box 69)
  - Girl from God's Country [833]., 1940. (Box 128)
  - The Girl from Havana [1034]., 1940. (Box 133)
  - The Girl from Mandalay [3504]., 1936. (Box 96, 99)
  - Girl from Panama [1922].; sw: Jack Townley; series: Estelita Special., 1951 (Box 134, 139)
  - The Girl Who Dared [1261].; sw: John K. Butler., 1944 (Box 111, 124)
  - Girls of the Big House [1480].; sw: Houston Branch; series: Anniversary., 1945 (Box 100)
  - Git Along Little Dogies [606]., 1937. (Box 104)
  - G.I. War Brides [1640].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Victory., 1946 (Box 135)
  - Gobs and Gals [1921].; sw: Arthur T. Hornman; series: New Master Group., 1951 (Box 108, 126, 134)
  - Gobs in Blue [1080]., 1941. (Box 64)
  - The Golden Herd [1940].; sw: John Meredyth Lucas; series: Deluxe., 1952 (Box 87)
  - The Golden Stallion [1830].; sw: Sloan Nibley; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1949 (Box 111)
  - The Golden Tide [1669].; sw: James Edward Grant; series: Deluxe., 1950 (Box 122)
  - Gone With the Draft [1923].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1951 (Box 134)
  - Goodnight Sweetheart [1167]., 1944. (Box 92)
  - Grand Canyon Trail [1625].; sw: Gerald Geraghty; series: Premiere-Trucolor., 1948 (Box 122)
  - Grand Ole Opry [992]., 1940. (Box 119)
  - Grandpa Goes to Town [959]., 1940. (Box 120)
  - The Great Stagecoach Robbery [1415].; sw: Randall Faye., 1944 (Box 111)
  - The Great Train Robbery [1059]., 1941 (Box 133)
  - Grissly's Millions [1268].; sw: Muriel Roy Bolton., 1944 (Box 82)
  - Gunmen of Abilene [1727].; sw: M. Coates Webster; series: Famous Western., 1949 (Box 117)
  - Gunsmoke Ranch [627].; series: Mesquiteers., 1937 (Box 70)
  - A Guy Could Change [1490].; sw: Al Martin; series: Anniversay., 1945 (Box 74)
  - Happy Go Lucky [3503]., 1936. (Box 99)
  - Harbor of Missing Men [1758].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1949 (Box 66)
  - Havana Rose [1911].; sw: Charles E. Roberts and Jack Townley; series: Estelita Special., 1951 (Box 108)
  - Headin' for God's Country [1168], 1943. (Box 91)
  - Headline News [882].; sw: Lionel Houser, Alice Altschuler; series: Jubilee., 1939 (Box 86)
  - Heart of the Golden West [1129].; series: Roy Rogers., 1942 (Box 69)
  - Heart of the Rio Grande [1106].; series: Gene Autry., 1942 (Box 69)
  - Heart of the Rockies [1837].; sw: Eric Taylor; series: Premiere Trucolor., 1950 (Box 79, 93)
  - Heart of Virginia [1644].; sw: Jerry Sackheim John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1947 (Box 121)
  - Heldorado [1524].; sw: Gerald Geraghty; series: Roy Rogers Premiere Special., 1946 (Box 88)
  - Hellfire [1012].; sw: Dorrell McGowan, Stuart E. McGowan., 1948 (Box 78)
  - Hell's Crossroads [1958]. sw: John K. Butler, Barry Shipman., 1956 (Box 95, 130)
  - Hell's Half Acre [1963].; sw: Steve Fisher; series: Deluxe., 1953 (Box 95, 107)
  - Hell's Outpost [1972].; sw: Kenneth Gamet., 1954 (Box 130)
  - Here Comes Elmer [1089]., 1943. (Box 67, 85)
  - Heroes of the Hills [718].; series: Mesquiteers., 1938 (Box 86)
  - Heroes of the Saddle [918].; series: Mesquiteers., 1939 (Box 73)
  - Hi, Neighbor [1150]., 1942. (Box 99)
  - The Hideout [1572].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Variety., 1948 (Box 123)
  - High Iron [1965].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Deluxe., 1953 (Box 69)
  - High School Daughters [1762].; sw: Robert Libott, Frank Burt, Bradford Ropes; series: Variety., 1949 (Box 101)
  - Hillbilly Story [727].; sw: Darrell and Stuart McGowan., 1938 (Box ?)
  - Hills of Oklahoma [1802].; sw: Olive Cooper; series: Paramount., 1949 (Box 107)
  - The Hit Parade [644]., 1937. (Box 105)
  - The Hit Parade of 1941 [977].; sw: Bradford Ropes and Maurice Leo and F. Hugh Herbert; series: Deluxe., 1940 (Box 73, 112)
  - Hit Parade of 1942 [1152]. (Box 99)
  - Hit Parade of 1947 [1491].; sw: Frank Gill, Jr., Mary Loos; series: Deluxe., 1946 (Box 74)
  - Hit Parade of 1950 [1971].; sw: Betty Reinhardt, Aubrey Wisberg, Lawrence Kimble; series: Deluxe. (Box 67)
  - Hitch Hike Lady [3537]., 1935. (Box 114)
  - Hitchhike to Happiness [1461].; sw: Jack Townley., 1944 (Box 113)
  - Home in Oklahoma [1520].; sw: Gerald Geraghty; series: Roy Rogers Premiere., 1946 (Box 71)
  - Home in Wyoming [1109].; series: Autry., 1942 (Box 67)
  - Home on the Prairie [803].; series: Autry., 1938 (Box 127)
  - Home on the Range [1585].; sw: Betty Burbridge; series: All-star Western., 1945 (Box 92)
  - Homicide for Three [1567].; sw: Bradbury Foote; series: Variety., 1948 (Box 123)
  - Honeychile [6030].; sw: Jack Townley, Charles E. Roberts; series: Judy Canova Special., 1950 (Box 99)
  - Honolulu Holiday [762].; sw: Norman Burnstine., 1938 (Box 126)
  - Hoodlum Empire [1794].; sw: Bruce Manning; series: Deluxe., 1951 (Box 67)
  - House by the River [1031].; sw: Mel Dinelli; series: Deluxe., 1949 (Box 133)
  - The House of Thousand Candles [3505]., 1935. (Box 114)
  - Hurrican Smith [1072]., 1941. (Box 119)
  - I Cover the Underworld [1990].; sw: John K. Butler; series: Jubilee., 1954 (Box 130)
  - I, Jane Doe [1674].; sw: Lawrence Kimble; series: Deluxe., 1947 (Box 62)
  - I Stand Accused [856]., 1938 (Box 70)
  - I was a Convict [839]., 1938. (Box 128)
  - Ice Capades [1073]., 1941. (Box 92, 117)
  - Ice Capades Review [1153]., 1942. (Box ?)
  - In Old Amarillo [1839].; sw: Sloan Nibley; series: Premiere., 1950 (Box 98)
  - In Old California [1142]., 1942. (Box 92)
  - In Old Cheyonne [925]., 1941. (Box 62)
  - In Old Missouri [984]., 1940. (Box 64)
  - In Old Monterey [802].; series: Autry., 1939 (Box 127)
  - In Old Sacramento [1464].; sw: Frances Hyland; series: Deluxe., 1945 (Box 100)
  - The Inner Circle [1552].; sw: Dorrell McGowan and Stuart E. McGowan; series: Jubillee., 1946 (Box 137)
  - Insurance Investigator [1901].; s w: Gertrude Walker; series: Variety., 1950 (Box 108)
  - The Invisible Informer [1553].; s w: Sherman L. Lowe; series: Jubilee., 1946 (Box 137)